"use strict";(self.webpackChunkreact_homework_template=self.webpackChunkreact_homework_template||[]).push([[273],{273:function(e,n,r){r.r(n),r.d(n,{default:function(){return c}});var s=r(433),t=r(439),a=r(791),o=JSON.parse('[{"question":"Question 1: What is the capital of France?","answers":["Paris","Berlin","London","Madrid"],"correctAnswers":["Paris"]},{"question":"Question 2: Which of the following are programming languages?","answers":["HTML","CSS","JavaScript","Python"],"correctAnswers":["JavaScript","Python"]},{"question":"Question 3: What is the largest planet in our solar system?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Earth","Saturn"],"correctAnswers":["Jupiter"]},{"question":"Question 4: Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Leonardo da Vinci","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh","Michelangelo"],"correctAnswers":["Leonardo da Vinci"]},{"question":"Question 5: How many continents are there in the world?","answers":["5","6","7","8"],"correctAnswers":["7"]},{"question":"Question 1: What is the capital of France?","answers":["Paris","Berlin","London","Madrid"],"correctAnswers":["Paris"]},{"question":"Question 2: Which of the following are programming languages?","answers":["HTML","CSS","JavaScript","Python"],"correctAnswers":["JavaScript","Python"]},{"question":"Question 3: What is the largest planet in our solar system?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Earth","Saturn"],"correctAnswers":["Jupiter"]},{"question":"Question 4: Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Leonardo da Vinci","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh","Michelangelo"],"correctAnswers":["Leonardo da Vinci"]},{"question":"Question 5: How many continents are there in the world?","answers":["5","6","7","8"],"correctAnswers":["7"]},{"question":"Question 1: What is the capital of France?","answers":["Paris","Berlin","London","Madrid"],"correctAnswers":["Paris"]},{"question":"Question 2: Which of the following are programming languages?","answers":["HTML","CSS","JavaScript","Python"],"correctAnswers":["JavaScript","Python"]},{"question":"Question 3: What is the largest planet in our solar system?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Earth","Saturn"],"correctAnswers":["Jupiter"]},{"question":"Question 4: Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Leonardo da Vinci","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh","Michelangelo"],"correctAnswers":["Leonardo da Vinci"]},{"question":"Question 5: How many continents are there in the world?","answers":["5","6","7","8"],"correctAnswers":["7"]},{"question":"Question 1: What is the capital of France?","answers":["Paris","Berlin","London","Madrid"],"correctAnswers":["Paris"]},{"question":"Question 2: Which of the following are programming languages?","answers":["HTML","CSS","JavaScript","Python"],"correctAnswers":["JavaScript","Python"]},{"question":"Question 3: What is the largest planet in our solar system?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Earth","Saturn"],"correctAnswers":["Jupiter"]},{"question":"Question 4: Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Leonardo da Vinci","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh","Michelangelo"],"correctAnswers":["Leonardo da Vinci"]},{"question":"Question 5: How many continents are there in the world?","answers":["5","6","7","8"],"correctAnswers":["7"]},{"question":"Question 1: What is the capital of France?","answers":["Paris","Berlin","London","Madrid"],"correctAnswers":["Paris"]},{"question":"Question 2: Which of the following are programming languages?","answers":["HTML","CSS","JavaScript","Python"],"correctAnswers":["JavaScript","Python"]},{"question":"Question 3: What is the largest planet in our solar system?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Earth","Saturn"],"correctAnswers":["Jupiter"]},{"question":"Question 4: Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Leonardo da Vinci","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh","Michelangelo"],"correctAnswers":["Leonardo da Vinci"]},{"question":"Question 5: How many continents are there in the world?","answers":["5","6","7","8"],"correctAnswers":["7"]}]'),i=r(184),c=function(){var e=(0,a.useState)(0),n=(0,t.Z)(e,2),r=n[0],c=n[1],u=(0,a.useState)([]),h=(0,t.Z)(u,2),l=h[0],w=h[1],d=(0,a.useState)(0),p=(0,t.Z)(d,2),g=p[0],f=p[1];return(0,i.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,i.jsx)("h1",{children:o[r].question}),o[r].answers.map((function(e,n){return(0,i.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,i.jsx)("input",{type:"checkbox",checked:l.includes(e),onChange:function(){return function(e){l.includes(e)?w(l.filter((function(n){return n!==e}))):w([].concat((0,s.Z)(l),[e]))}(e)}}),(0,i.jsx)("label",{children:e})]},n)})),(0,i.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){var e=0;if(o[r].correctAnswers.forEach((function(n){l.includes(n)&&e++})),f(g+(e===o[r].correctAnswers.length?1:0)),r<o.length-1)c(r+1);else{var n=o.map((function(e){return e.correctAnswers.join(", ")}));alert("Results:\n".concat(o.map((function(e,r){return"".concat(e.question,"\nCorrect answers: ").concat(n[r])})).join("\n\n"),"\n\nTotal correct answers: ").concat(g))}w([])},children:"Next Question"})]})}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=273.0ba27283.chunk.js.map